http://www.ibselectronics.com/privacy-policy/

Effective Date:  May 31, 2016This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.ibselectronics.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:What information we collect;With whom it is shared;How it can be corrected;How it is secured;How policy changes will be communicated; andHow to address concerns over misuse of personal data.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.IBS Electronics does NOT sell your personal informationYour name, company name, address, phone number, and email address are never sold to third parties.Notification of ChangesWhenever material changes are made to this privacy policy a revised privacy policy will be placed on this website.Other Provisions as Required by LawNumerous other provisions and/or practices may be required as a result of laws, international treaties, or industry practices. It is up to you to determine what additional practices must be followed and/or what additional disclosures are required. Please take special notice of the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA), which is frequently amended and now includes a disclosure requirement for “Do Not Track” signals.
What is considered personal information under the CA privacy law that will need to be deleted?
California consumers can request a business delete their personal information under California’s new privacy law beginning January 1, 2020. The covered personal information includes information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (714-660-1793)  or via email, (info@ibselectronics.com)
Join our Email List
